[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "front": "Can I do it later?",
    "back": "Kann ich es später machen? ",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "front": "I don't really know how to do that",
    "back": "Ich weiß wirklich nicht, wie ich das machen soll",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "front": "It's my first day",
    "back": "Ich bin mir nicht Sicher",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "front": "I need more time off",
    "back": "Ich weiß wirklich nicht, wie ich das machen soll",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "front": "I don't wanna work",
    "back": "Ich habe keine lust",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "front": "Can I get you something to drink?",
    "back": "Kann ich dir etwas zu trinken anbienten?",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "front": "I'm hungry",
    "back": "Was hast du gestern gemacht?",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "front": "Can't someone else do it?",
    "back": "Was hast du gestern gemacht?",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "front": "I'm sick",
    "back": "Ich bin krank",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "front": "let's go to the cinema",
    "back": "Lass uns ins Kino gehen",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "front": "Where is the disco?",
    "back": "Das ist nicht richtig",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "front": "I have no idea",
    "back": "Keine Ahnung!",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "front": "I'm free tomorrow",
    "back": "Ich bin morgen frei",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "front": "I'm sick'",
    "back": "Ich brauche mehr Urlaub",
    "tags": ["social"]
  },
  {
    "id": 1,
    "front": "Maybe next time",
    "back": "Vielleicht beim nächsten Mal",
    "tags": ["social"]
  }
]
